{
    "subject": "Henri-Georges_Clouzot",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Manon__film_",
    "human_readable": "Henri-Georges Clouzot directed the film Manon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9744513034820557,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8878424167633057,
            "question": "Can you tell me the title of a movie directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.833903968334198,
            "question": "What film did Henri-Georges Clouzot direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7984061241149902,
            "question": "What films has Henri-Georges Clouzot made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7848675847053528,
            "question": "Who directed the film Manon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208200454711914,
            "question": "Is Manon a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5925251841545105,
            "question": "Who was responsible for directing Manon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4921087622642517,
            "question": "Is Manon a famous film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2749837040901184,
            "question": "What genre is the film Manon likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2227131873369217,
            "question": "What is the name of the film director?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henri-Georges Clouzot directed the film Manon.",
            "html": "yago_23828_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Manon likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_23828_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Manon a famous film?",
            "html": "yago_23828_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was responsible for directing Manon?",
            "html": "yago_23828_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23828_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Henri-Georges Clouzot directed the film Manon. This is confirmed by multiple sources, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23828/re-ranker-msmarco/51.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23828/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents confirm that Henri-Georges Clouzot directed the film \"Manon,\" which was released in 1949 and is an adaptation of Abb\u00e9 Pr\u00e9vost's novel."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}